[{"id":"26","type":"bool","ref":"Ether 15:11","question":"The hill Cumorah was referred as the hill Ramah by the Jaredites.","answer":"true","options":["true","false"]},{"id":"27","type":"bool","ref":"Mor 1:3, 4:23","question":"The hill Cumorah was referred as the hill Shim by the Nephites.","answer":"true","options":["true","false"]},{"id":"28","type":"fill","ref":"Look at Book of Mormon","question":"In what beautiful state, is the hill Cumorah located.","answer":"New York","options":["fill"]},{"id":"56","type":"fill","ref":"Ask someone that knows","question":"What is the name of cont1nent in which the book was deposited and in which we in the united states live?","answer":"North America","options":["fill"]},{"id":"65","type":"bool","ref":"No ref because they are not.","question":"The Urim and Thummim are mentioned by name in the text of Book of Mormon?","answer":"false","options":["true","false"]},{"id":"133","type":"fill","ref":"Look at Book of Mormon","question":"What is the name of the artist who painted most of the Book of Mormon paintings?","answer":["Arnold","Friberg"],"options":["fill"]},{"id":"134","type":"multi","ref":"Testimony of Three Witnesses","question":"Who were the Three Witnesses of the Book of Mormon.","answer":"Oliver Cowdery, David Whitmer and Martin Harris","options":["Oliver Cowdery, David Whitmer and Lorenzo Snow","Joseph Smith Sr, Brigham Young and Nephi","Oliver Cowdery, David Whitmer and Martin Harris"]},{"id":"135","type":"bool","ref":"Testimony of the Eight Witnesses","question":"In the testimony of the Eight Witnesses, they describe the plates of having the appearance of ancient work, and of curious workmanship.","answer":"true","options":["true","false"]},{"id":"136","type":"bool","ref":"Testimony of the Eight Witnesses","question":"In the testimony of the Eight Witnesses, they state that they gave their names to the world, to witness unto the world that, that they handled the plates with their hands and saw the engraving thereon.","answer":"true","options":["true","false"]},{"id":"137","type":"fill","ref":"Testimony of the Eight Witnesses","question":"The Eight Witnesses state that they “lie not” and bear witness unto whom?","answer":"god","options":["fill"]},{"id":"138","type":"fill","ref":"Book of Mormon","question":"What is the title of the first book in the Book of Mormon?","answer":"Nephi","options":["fill"]},{"id":"139","type":"fill","ref":"Book of Mormon","question":"What is the title of the last book in the Book of Mormon?","answer":"Moroni","options":["fill"]},{"id":"140","type":"bool","ref":"Book of Mormon","question":"The longest book in the Book of Mormon is the Book of Mosiah?","answer":"false","options":["true","false"]},{"id":"141","type":"fill","ref":"Book of Mormon","question":"What is the longest book in the Book of Mormon","answer":"Alma","options":["fill"]},{"id":"142","type":"fill","ref":"Book of Mormon","question":"What Book of Mormon book has the least verses","answer":"Jarom","options":["fill"]},{"id":"143","type":"fill","ref":"Book of Mormon","question":"What is the name of the book that has the second least amount of verses","answer":"The Words Of Mormon","options":["fill"]},{"id":"144","type":"multi","ref":"Book of Mormon","question":"The words: “was the son of “are used how many times in the Book of Ether.","answer":"21","options":["15","20","21"]},{"id":"145","type":"fill","ref":"Book of Omni","question":"What Book of Mormon author wrote the least amount of words in the Book of Mormon?","answer":"Chemish","options":["fill"]},{"id":"146","type":"fill","ref":"Book of Omni","question":"This Book of Mormon author only wrote one verse.","answer":"Chemish","options":["fill"]},{"id":"148","type":"bool","ref":"Abish-Alma19:16, Eve-1Nep5:11, Isabel-Alma39:3, Mary-Mos3:8, Sariah-1Nep2:5","question":"There are only three women mentioned by name in the Book of Mormon.","answer":"false","options":["true","false"]},{"id":"159","type":"fill","ref":"Book of Mormon","question":"The record that Nephi made about his reign and ministry is known to us as the: “First Book Of _____”.","answer":"Nephi","options":["fill"]},{"id":"527","type":"bool","ref":"1 Nep11:23","question":"The angel said that the love of God is the most joyous to the soul.","answer":"true","options":["true","false"]},{"id":"563","type":"fill","ref":"Book of Mormon Pictures","question":"What animal appears in the Book of Mormon picture where Lehi is holding the Liahona?","answer":"Camal","options":["fill"]},{"id":"676","type":"bool","ref":"1Neh19:6","question":"Nephi only wrote the things that he deemed sacred upon the plates.","answer":"true","options":["true","false"]},{"id":"783","type":"fill","ref":"3Nep3:11","question":"The Lord will give power to the seer to bring forth his word unto the seed of _____ loins.","answer":"Joseph","options":["fill"]},{"id":"1064","type":"bool","ref":"Nep26:23","question":"Nephi wrote: “For behold, my beloved brethren, I say unto you that the Lord God works not in darkness”.","answer":"true","options":["true","false"]},{"id":"1175","type":"multi","ref":"Nep29:8","question":"The Lord said:  “Know ye not that the testimony of _____ nations is a witness unto you that I am God, and that I remember one nation like unto another”.","answer":"Two","options":["Two","Twenty","Four"]},{"id":"1478","type":"bool","ref":"Look at your dictionary","question":"An allegory is the expression by means of symbolic fictional figures and actions of truths or generalizations about human existence.","answer":"true","options":["true","false"]},{"id":"1590","type":"fill","ref":"7:21","question":"The multitude fell to the _____ when God showed his power to the multitude.","answer":"Earth, &&&","options":["fill"]},{"id":"1684","type":"fill","ref":"Book of Jarom","question":"What was Enos’ son name that was also a record keeper?","answer":"Jarom","options":["fill"]},{"id":"1685","type":"bool","ref":"Book of Jarom","question":"The Book of Jarom has only one chapter.","answer":"true","options":["true","false"]},{"id":"1686","type":"fill","ref":"Book of Jarom","question":"What Book of Mormon historian/record keeper wrote the fewest verses in his book?","answer":"Jarom","options":["fill"]},{"id":"1731","type":"bool","ref":"Book of Omni","question":"There is only one chapter of Omni in the Book of Mormon.","answer":"true","options":["true","false"]},{"id":"1794","type":"fill","ref":"Ether12:1 & 14:24","question":"Coriantumr was a descendant of what tribe of people?","answer":"Jaredites","options":["fill"]},{"id":"1823","type":"multi","ref":"3-4","question":"The strong and mighty man that went up to the wilderness was_____.","answer":"Zeniff","options":["Nephi","Zeniff","Zenos"]},{"id":"1838","type":"multi","ref":"Mormon1:4","question":"Mormon found the plates pleasing unto him because it conta1ned the prophecies of the coming of_____.","answer":"Christ","options":["Abraham","Nephi","Christ"]},{"id":"1847","type":"bool","ref":"W of Mor1:7","question":"Mormon knew all things and things which are to come.","answer":"false","options":["true","false"]},{"id":"1848","type":"multi","ref":"Mor1:8","question":"Mormon prayed to_____ concerning the Lamanites; that they may once again come to the knowledge of God and the redemption of Christ.","answer":"God","options":["Holy Ghost","The Stars","God"]},{"id":"1849","type":"multi","ref":"Mormon1:8","question":"Mormon prayed to God concerning the Lamanites; that they may once again be a_____ people.","answer":"Delightsome","options":["Nice","Delightsome","Kind"]},{"id":"1851","type":"multi","ref":"Mormon1:9","question":"Mormon proceeding with the record and made it according to the knowledge and the_____ which God had given him.","answer":"Understanding.","options":["Gift","Power","Understanding."]},{"id":"1853","type":"multi","ref":"Mormon1:10","question":"Wherefore it came to pass that_____ had delivered these plates into the hands of King Benjamin.","answer":"Amaleki","options":["Mormon","Nephi","Amaleki"]},{"id":"1858","type":"multi","ref":"Mormon1:11","question":"The things written on Mormon’s record and the other plates were important because the Nephites and their brethren would be judged at the great and_____ day.","answer":"Last","options":["Gloomy","Last","Glorious"]},{"id":"1873","type":"multi","ref":"Mormon1:17","question":"During the reign of King Benjamin there were many holy men in the land, and they spoke with the power and_____ of God.","answer":"Authority","options":["Authority","Gift","Knowledge"]},{"id":"1877","type":"multi","ref":"Nep5:20","question":"Mormon was a pure descendant of whom?","answer":"Lehi","options":["Laman","Nephi","Lehi"]},{"id":"2009","type":"fill","ref":"6,8","question":"Who did King Benjamin say would cast out devils, or the evil spirits which shall dwell in the hearts of the children of men?  Jesus -","answer":"Mo3:","options":["fill"]},{"id":"2010","type":"fill","ref":"7-8","question":"Who did King Benjamin say shall suffer temptations, and pain of body, thirst, and fatigue, even more than man can suffer?  Jesus -","answer":"Mos3:","options":["fill"]},{"id":"2084","type":"multi","ref":"5Mos3:26","question":"Who had spoken to King Benjamin and told him to tell the people not to bring upon themselves a never-ending torment; that they may not drink out of the cup of wrath of God?.","answer":"An Angel","options":["An Angel","Nephi","Enos"]},{"id":"2111","type":"multi","ref":"4,5","question":"How many days did Ammon and his brethren wonder in the wilderness before they came to a hill; which is north of the land of Shilom, and pitched their tents.","answer":"40","options":["40","50","60"]},{"id":"2112","type":"multi","ref":"-(B)","question":"Of the party of sixteen men that went with Ammon, only himself and_____ of his brethren met with the king of the people of the land of Nephi/Shilom.","answer":"&&&","options":["2","3"]},{"id":"2170","type":"fill","ref":"11-12","question":"King Limhi asked_____ if he was able to translate the twenty-four plates that his people had brought back and in if he knew of anyone that could.  Ammon-","answer":"Mos8:","options":["fill"]},{"id":"2304","type":"fill","ref":"12-13","question":"The land that King Noah possessed and caused that a very high tower be built was called_____.  Shilom-","answer":"Mos11:","options":["fill"]},{"id":"2307","type":"multi","ref":"12,13","question":"What was the name of the land that had been a resort for the Nephites when they were told by the Lord to flee into the wilderness?","answer":"Nephi","options":["Shilom","Shemlon","Nephi"]},{"id":"2590","type":"multi","ref":"13,18","question":"Who gave Alma1 the authority to baptize people in the Waters of Mormon?","answer":"Almighty God","options":["Almighty God","Nephi","Moses"]},{"id":"2663","type":"multi","ref":"11,12","question":"How many times did the Nephites battle with the Lamanites and were beaten and suffered much loss before they returned to the city of Nephi?","answer":"3","options":["1","2","3"]},{"id":"2830","type":"multi","ref":"6,7","question":"Because the Lord blessed the people they began to prosper and became numerous and began to scatter upon the face of the_____.","answer":"Earth","options":["Earth","World","Globe"]},{"id":"3168","type":"fill","ref":"20,21","question":"Alma2 said that the course of the Lord is one eternal_____ and he does not dwell in unholy temples.   Round-","answer":"Alma7:","options":["fill"]},{"id":"3206","type":"bool","ref":"Check the end of chapter 8","question":"Chapters 9 though 14 in the Book of Alma comprise the words and teachings inclusively that were delivered to the people who were in the land of Ammonihah.","answer":"true","options":["true","false"]},{"id":"3236","type":"fill","ref":"9,10","question":"Amulek believed that_____ was a holy man because an angel of the Lord had told him so and knew that the things that the he had said were true.  Alma-","answer":"Alma10:","options":["fill"]},{"id":"3364","type":"multi","ref":"14-17","question":"How many times did the chief judge of the land smack Alma2 and Amulek on their cheeks?","answer":"1","options":["1","2","3"]},{"id":"3384","type":"fill","ref":"12-13","question":"Zeezrom was baptized by_____ and afterward, he began to preach the word of God in the land of Sidom.  Alma-","answer":"Alma15:","options":["fill"]},{"id":"3388","type":"multi","ref":"15:16","question":"How many people of Amulek's household were converted to the gospel?____","answer":"1","options":["1","2","3"]},{"id":"3412","type":"bool","ref":"Beginning of Alma17","question":"Chapters 17 though 26 in the Book of Alma contain the account of the sons of King Mosiah inclusively.","answer":"true","options":["true","false"]},{"id":"3439","type":"multi","ref":"26-27","question":"How many days had Ammon been a servant unto King Lamoni when some Lamanites came and scattered his flock?","answer":"2","options":["2","3","4"]},{"id":"3459","type":"fill","ref":"5-6","question":"King_____ was taught by his father that there was a Great Spirit; and feared that it had come down because he had slain so many of his servants for letting the Lamanites scatter his flocks.  Lamoni-","answer":"Alma18:","options":["fill"]},{"id":"3476","type":"fill","ref":"24-25","question":"King Lamoni did not know what Ammon meant when he asked him if he believed that there was a_____.  God-","answer":"Alma18:","options":["fill"]},{"id":"3505","type":"fill","ref":"9-10","question":"The wife of King Lamoni believed all the words of_____; and because of her exceeding faith she would be blessed.  Ammon-","answer":"Alma19:","options":["fill"]},{"id":"3523","type":"fill","ref":"29-28","question":"Abish took the_____ by the hand; and as soon as she touched her hand she stood up and thanked Jesus for saving her from an awful hell.  Queen-","answer":"Alma19:","options":["fill"]},{"id":"3525","type":"fill","ref":"29,30","question":"Who took King Lamoni by the hand and he stood upon his feet?  Abish-Alma19:","answer":"16,","options":["fill"]},{"id":"3568","type":"fill","ref":"16-17","question":"And it came to pass that Aaron and his brethren were blessed by the Lord and brought many of the_____ and Lamanites to the knowledge of the truth.   Amalekites-","answer":"Alma21:","options":["fill"]},{"id":"3728","type":"multi","ref":"2,7","question":"During the fifteenth year of the reign of the judges over the people of Nephi; the most tremendous_____ occurred in Nephites history.","answer":"War","options":["War","Confrontation","Battle"]},{"id":"3736","type":"multi","ref":"13,14","question":"Mormon says that there is a great call of diligence of men to labor in the_____ of the Lord because of the power of the devil.","answer":"Workshop, &&&","options":["Workshop","Vineyard","Neither"]},{"id":"3841","type":"multi","ref":"45,48","question":"How many times did Korihor deny that there was a God?","answer":"1","options":["1","2","3"]},{"id":"3992","type":"fill","ref":"15,17","question":"What second prophet of old did Alma2 say had testified of the Son of God and because the people would not understand his words; they stoned him to death?  Zenock","answer":"Alma33:","options":["fill"]},{"id":"4040","type":"multi","ref":"16,18","question":"Who did Amulek say “is mighty to save”?","answer":"Nephi","options":["Nephi","Moses"]},{"id":"4041","type":"multi","ref":"20,21","question":"Amulek told his brethren to cry unto the Lord in their fields, over all of their flocks and in their_____.","answer":"Yards","options":["Yards","Barns","Houses"]},{"id":"4145","type":"multi","ref":"19,18","question":"The Lord had _____ on Alma2 that he could no longer remember the memory of his sins.","answer":"Compassion","options":["Compassion","Love","Mercy"]},{"id":"4161","type":"multi","ref":"27,26","question":"Alma2 said that he puts his_____ in God, and he will still deliver him from his many trials and troubles.","answer":"Love","options":["Love","Trust","Whole Soul"]},{"id":"4223","type":"fill","ref":"37:38","question":"Another name that we can use to describe the Interpreters is a ball or director and the fathers of Alma2 and Helaman called it the_____.  Liahona-Alma37:","answer":"24,","options":["fill"]},{"id":"4225","type":"multi","ref":"26-27","question":"Alma2 told Helaman that Jaredites were destroyed because they did not_____; therefore the word of the Lord had been fulfilled.","answer":"Care","options":["Care","Repent","Pray"]},{"id":"4281","type":"fill","ref":"37:1","question":"What is the name of Alma2 the Youngers’ second son?  Shiblon-Alma38:","answer":"1,","options":["fill"]},{"id":"4556","type":"multi","ref":"62:35","question":"The word Stratagem is used how many times in the book of Alma?","answer":"1","options":["1","5","7"]},{"id":"4590","type":"fill","ref":"5,6","question":"Moroni commanded_____ in the name of that all-powerful God, to deliver up their weapons of war.  Zerahemnah-","answer":"Alma44:","options":["fill"]},{"id":"4625","type":"fill","ref":"4,5","question":"Alma2 asked Helaman if he believed in Jesus_____, who shall come; and he said he believed in all the words which had been spoken unto him by Alma2.  Christ-","answer":"Alma45:","options":["fill"]},{"id":"4626","type":"multi","ref":"6,7","question":"Alma2 asked Helaman if he would keep his commandments, and he said he would with all his_____.","answer":"Mind","options":["Mind","Heart","Body"]},{"id":"4790","type":"fill","ref":"23-24","question":"The Nephites would not suffer that their wives and children should be massacred by the barbarous cruelty of the_____; who were once their brethren.  Lamanites-","answer":"Alma48:","options":["fill"]},{"id":"4868","type":"bool","ref":"alma50:35","question":"The people of Morianton were very stubborn because of his wickedness and his flattering words.","answer":"true","options":["true","false"]},{"id":"5056","type":"multi","ref":"Alam55:17","question":"Captain Moroni had the Nephite women and children and all of those that were able to use a weapon of war armed; and this was all done in profound_____.","answer":"Silence","options":["Loudness","Silence","Darkness"]},{"id":"5059","type":"fill","ref":"21,22","question":"And it came to pass that Captain Moroni had his people surround the armies of the_____, and this was done at night, so when the Lamanites awoke they saw that they were surrounded by the Nephites.  Lamanites-","answer":"Alma55:","options":["fill"]},{"id":"5094","type":"multi","ref":"41,42","question":"How many times did the Lamanites stop and rest than started again in pursuit of Helaman’s army before Helaman and his army decided to go to battle against them?","answer":"1","options":["1","2","3"]},{"id":"5361","type":"fill","ref":"Narrow","question":"Hagoth built himself a ship and went with many Nephites into the west sea, by the_____neck which led into the land northward.","answer":"Alma63:5-6","options":["fill"]},{"id":"5377","type":"multi","ref":"4:12","question":"The game of BOM Quest was inspired in part by the author’s _____.","answer":"no","options":["Wife","Mother","Ether"]}]